invesco.com 2007-06-30

# INVESCO - Privacy Policy

## Legal

#### INVESCO PLC Privacy Policy

INVESCO PLC (INVESCO) is committed to maintaining the absolute privacy of the information you share with us when you use this Web site. Information about invesco.com users is not sold to third parties. In the following statement, we describe what information is gathered from this site and how we use it. On www.invesco.com, we provide links to the Web sites of our business groups, which have their own privacy statements. If you visit those sites, please remember to read the privacy statements.

#### Information we gather on this Web site.

We gather two types of information on this site: personal information and general information about how the site is being used.

When you fill out the "Contact Us" page or request an Investor Kit or Press Kit, we ask for minimal personal information, such as your name, address, phone number, and e-mail address.

General Web site-tracking information, including statistics on which pages are viewed at what times, is gathered automatically by the Web server software. This software does not identify individual users, and it does not connect the personal data that may be provided by you to any Web-tracking statistics or report.

#### How we use the information.

The personal information you provide lets us know how to contact you to answer your questions or respond to your requests.

The general Web site tracking information is used to give us a summary view of our site, not to track individual users. We analyze the data to determine how to make the site better and more useful to our users. It is strictly for our internal use.

#### Our policy on sharing site information with third parties.

We are committed to maintaining your privacy. Information about users of www.invesco.com is not sold to any third party.
